(Yowayowa Sensei)
What a beautiful morning.
(Episode 5: Yowayowa Date)
On the second night of the school camping trip,
Sensei said she likes me.
I… like you too.
Even though she only sees me as a student,
at least I can be sure
she has a good impression of me.
Abikura-kun.
S… Sensei?
Her outfit is so cute.
Good… good morning. Are you heading out?
I… I'm not
PANICKED
going to buy something important.
Yowayowa-Sensei is even weak at lying.
Is she going on a date with her lover?
Akihito, what are you doing here?
Hurry up and get changed.
PULLS OUT
We're going on a date with Hiyo!
She's going out with my sister?
Wait, am I going too?
Don't you want to go?
I want to go.
Is Abikura-kun coming too?
She… she seems repelled.
Does she already dislike me
after a few days?
You don't want him to go, Hiyo?
No… no, it's not that
I don't want him to come along.
But we're going to buy "that stuff".
It's not appropriate for a teacher
to go out privately with students.
Hiyo, you're overthinking again.
Precisely because you're the teacher,
you should have
a grasp of students' personal lives too.
That's what I think.
DIZZY
You've got a point.
Then let's go on a date, Abikura-kun.
She's been brainwashed again.
Akihito, you look so handsome.
After all, it's a date.
You should dress up.
I bet she dressed up Sensei
just like this.
Here we are.
In the neighboring town,
we won't run into other students.
This way, you can be at ease, Hiyo.
TOUCHED
Ms. Akemi,
th… thank you.
My sister did this to help Sensei relax?
Well done, Akemi.
As a teacher,
she might indeed be concerned about
students' opinions when shopping.
LOCK EYES
LOOKS AWAY
DEVASTATED
She's definitely acting strange.
She seems so distant to me.
NERVOUS
I thought we'd gotten closer at the school camping trip.
Was it just my imagination?
Let's go shopping then.
Swimsuits.
We agreed to go to the beach next time.
Try on these two.
I'll help you put it on.
HEART RACING
I really shouldn't have come.
Why did my sister invite me along?
Wait, Hiyo,
what's up with that underwear?
No… it's not what you think.
It's just…
- Let me take a look.
- Today's her off day,
so she must be wearing
that set of lingerie.
Why?
Why is there a hole here?
Explain it to me.
Wait…
BLUSHING
TA-DA
We're all set.
Why did Akemi have to show it to me?
How is it? It suits her, right?
Is… is this really okay?
Going out privately with a student
to buy swimsuits…
Hiyo, you're super cute.
I think Akihito would be happy
to be your student.
BRAINWASHED
Is… is that so?
Stop brainwashing her.
Next is this one.
The pattern is so cute.
PATTING HEAD
Hiyo looks like a baby in this one.
It's so cute!
- Patting…
- Don't make Sensei wear a swimsuit like that.
Ms. Akemi!
I'm not a baby!
True enough.
I should pick something more mature.
Then try this one.
The contrast between childish
and mature ones is making me feel odd.
You were odd to begin with.
This one is so cute.
But I don't know if they have my size.
Mukubayashi?
Why did we run into her in another town?
We got a problem, Akemi!
My classmate is here as well.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
COLLAPSE
It's occupied.
Have we met before?
Have we?
By the way, are you a beauty?
You're so cute!
S-sorry…
I-it's fine, I'm partly to blame.
It's really hot in here.
I feel this wave of heat.
What exactly did you do
in here earlier, Akemi?
I'm sorry, my sister is so pushy.
It's okay.
U-um, Sensei…
You seem distant with me today.
Are you hiding something from me?
Did I do something wrong?
W-What…
C-can't I cover it?
She misinterpreted?
D-do you want to see it?
B-but I'm so embarrassed.
You can cover that.
Feels like it got even hotter.
We're back.
So, later on…
Boys aren't allowed on the next part.
Wait here for us.
You didn't stop me
when you bought swimsuits!
We tried to avoid Mukubayashi
and went straight home after shopping.
KEEPING DISTANCE
Sensei still seems a bit distant,
but our precious date ended just like that.
KEEPING DISTANCE
I don't want her to go home.
I'll make dinner then.
Hiyo, stay and eat with us.
I-I shouldn't impose…
You already drove me today.
I can't possibly…
Don't worry about it.
I bet you didn't eat properly yesterday.
I-I was busy with post-camp cleanup.
BITING
So I just had a plain slice of toast.
You ate it plain?
BITING
See?
Then I'll help you out.
No.
Aren't your finals coming up?
Since Hiyo's here,
why not have her tutor you?
But I can't ask for tutoring
on her day off.
Are you going to study?
I'll help you.
OVERJOYED
Sh-she looks so happy.
STARING
Sh-she keeps staring at my face.
But I solved all the problems instantly,
and there's nothing I need help with.
English is the subject I work hardest on.
U-um…
Yes?
I'm not sure if I got this part right.
Let me check it out.
This part?
HEART RACING
CORRECT
You did great! Here's a credit.
I got a credit.
But you mistranslated this.
Oh no.
I thought I got everything right.
Seems you're not great
at long reading comprehension.
Let's analyze it sentence by sentence.
O-okay.
All correct!
You'll definitely ace your finals.
Thank you.
Sensei really is good at teaching.
And she pays close attention
to her students.
Once we clear up
those awful misunderstandings,
she'll become an outstanding teacher
she dreams of being.
Now then…
W-we've finished reviewing for the exam.
I-I should give you a reward.
C-come here, Abikura-kun.
What?
Sh-she's sitting on my bed
and telling me to come over.
A-Abikura-kun…
What is it?
Wait, what exactly is happening here?
Sensei, what are you doing?
Eh?
Ms. Akemi told me
that unless I let you rest on my lap
while soothing you with a handbell,
you wouldn't be happy.
Anyone could tell that's nonsense.
Honestly, I suspected she was tricking me.
Great.
Well, uh…
This is for you.
TO ABIKURA-KUN
F… for me?
It's a premium mechanical pencil.
It's easier on the hand.
The lead advances automatically.
I went out today to buy this.
Sorry for keeping it secret.
I've always wanted
to thank you with a gift.
You helped me during the test of courage,
found my handouts,
a…and so many other things.
PATTING HEAD
You worked so hard
during the school camping trip.
Thank you for always helping me.
Sensei?
Boys grow up so fast.
Akemi?
But it's okay.
Anyone can become a baby again.
Alright, you carry on.
Carry on with what?
TO ABIKURA-KUN
I received a gift from Sensei.
(Yowayowa Sensei)
After the school camping trip,
we took final exams.
Kowakowa… no.
Good morning, Hiwamura-sensei.
A… a student greeted Sensei first?
Did the test of courage actually work?
M… morning.
She's still scary,
but she's probably a good teacher.
Since returning
from the school camping trip,
things have started to change.
You were really cool
during the test of courage, class president.
Everyone seems nicer to me too.
CLASS 2-2
The only thing that didn't change…
Mukubayashi, Yukishita,
time for your remedial lessons.
CRYING
This is brutal.
I'm really sorry.
I announced the scope of test
and made the questions easier,
but you still failed.
GRADING PAPERS
But Yukishita,
you really can't doodle on the answer sheet.
GRADING PAPERS
I couldn't understand any of it. So I was bored.
Not only have I failed finals,
during the school camping trip,
I couldn't be of use at all.
I'm completely worthless.
Mu…Mukubayashi.
No.
Didn't you help me decorate
for the test of courage?
Anyone could've done that!
That's not true.
Why are you here anyway?
Because I'm exceptional.
SCORED 95 IN ENGLISH
Sensei asked me to tutor.
Did you appear in the women's bath
also because you're exceptional?
I'm really sorry about that.
As for the school camping trip,
I'm also grateful to you, Mukubayashi.
You're always so strong.
You're my role model.
So let's study together
and pass this makeup test.
TOUCHED
Hiyori…
Okay! I'll get full score
on the makeup test!
She bounced back fast.
Where is that earlier spirit?
Is it really that hard?
I just can't memorize it.
At this rate, they'll never
pass the makeup test.
Why not associate it
with something memorable?
Oh, right.
Um… why am I wearing this?
Wait, Yuki.
That's lingerie!
Lately I keep seeing Sensei
in outfits like this.
If I could write vocabulary
on a woman's body,
I'd memorize them because it's so lewd.
What's she even saying?
Go ahead, write on her, Abikura.
Why me?
I realized
it's more lewd when you do it.
Pervert! Lecher!
This is definitely not normal.
Exactly.
I'll hold it steady,
so you can write better.
SHOVING
Please write, Abikura-kun.
If this helps Yukishita
remember the words,
I can make a little sacrifice.
No.
She definitely just
wants to see something pervy.
B… but Mukubayashi seems excited too.
This might actually work.
TOUCHING
STARTLED
WILLING
LIMP
I-I can actually memorize it this way.
Wanna try writing it then?
WILLING TO DO SOMETHING
No way.
I feel a bit more confident now.
Because of what we just did?
Because I'm an idiot.
I really can't remember any English words.
But seeing how far Hiyori would go for us,
I want to repay her efforts.
I have to get a good score
on the makeup test.
So let's do this together, Yuki!
TEARING
Alright, Abikura, just write.
Why do I have to write?
It has to be a guy, so I'll be
embarrassed enough to memorize it.
Th-this will really help them
pass the makeup test?
That tickles.
SLIPS
RECOILS
I never said you could touch there!
Am I gonna die after this?
STRENGTH
I've memorized them all.
You are amazing.
Let's keep working like this.
A FEW DAYS LATER
This method actually worked.
They scored perfectly
A FEW DAYS LATER
on the English vocabulary section of the makeup test.
It's so late
after the class president meeting.
Something's on the floor?
This is… Sensei's hairpin.
Is she so weak that she got kidnapped?
Sensei?
HIWAMURA
SHIVERING
Sensei?
TREMBLING, DEEP BREATHING
She's training alone again.
By the way,
isn't that a school swimsuit?
Come on, Sensei.
You even cherish that old school swimsuit?
HEART RACING
Um, Sensei?
Look out!
STARTLED
A-Abikura-kun?
S-sorry!
You protected me again.
No,
I shouldn't have called out suddenly.
Sorry about that.
This was on the floor.
My hairpin.
Thank you.
Are you training again?
Yes.
Because I'm not a good swimmer,
I borrowed the pool to practice.
If a student were drowning in front of me,
I would be able to rescue them.
Again, she's doing this for her students.
But didn't you just buy a new swimsuit?
Th-that one…
I want to save it for
when I go to the beach with Ms. Akemi.
My high school swimsuit still fits me,
so I figured I'd wear this one for now.
TIGHT
Does it really still fit?
No, Sensei just treasures these items.
Thinking it's weird for adults
to wear school swimsuits
or that it's a bit lewd,
that's what's actually wrong.
Probably.
Oh,
there's a stretching move
that I need help with.
Could you help me?
Of course.
LIES DOWN
Hold my hands between your knees,
so I can't move.
Then rub here to help me relax.
Where… exactly?
Right here, below the shoulder,
near the armpit.
It's a stretch where you press down
to relax the muscles.
That's really elaborate.
Uh, hold your hands between the knees
and rub here?
No, this isn't right.
This position isn't right
in every possible way.
SIGHS
I'm much more relaxed.
Then, unsurprisingly,
Sensei got tired during warm-ups.
But if she does professional warm-ups,
maybe she's actually good at swimming?
Besides, swimming's mandatory in school.
Nowadays, the majority of people can swim.
Sensei!
S-sorry.
Actually, I'm even afraid
of water touching my face.
And my body won't float at all.
Is she this bad at swimming?
How can you practice alone then?
You need someone to watch over you.
T-that's true.
Actually, I learned a little before.
I might be able to teach you the basics.
But you'll be going home late.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
A… Abikura-kun.
Let's start with floating practice.
You can hold onto the edge of the pool.
Try to relax.
Remember the feeling of floating.
O-okay.
What's wrong?
I'm just thinking
that if my hand slips,
I'll sink to the bottom.
FLOATING
SPLASH
She definitely will.
So, um…
Can you hold my hands?
HEART POUNDING
O-okay.
But she still isn't floating.
Once she lifts her legs,
her head sinks.
GURGLING
Her motor skills are really weak.
L-Let's take a break, Sensei.
N-no.
I have no strength
to stand in the water anymore.
FLOATING
Eh? Am I floating?
I'm finally floating!
Because she's too tired,
she is finally relaxed?
But this view is a bit…
SPLITS
SCREAMS
Her swimsuit couldn't hold on anymore.
I got something valuable.